symbios.pk 2012-05-25

# Pakistan's Top Online Shop, Nokia, Blackberry, Apple, Casio, Sony, Canon & Much More

Symbios a company incorporated in Pakistan, is a member of the e-group.

The purpose of this statement is to set out how we use personal information that we may obtain about you. By either registering as a user of any services provided by Argos on this website and by using the Argos website generally you agree to this use.

**Use of your Personal Information**

  1. When you register and use this site:  

    * You will be asked to provide certain information such as your contact details. We will store this data and hold it on computers or otherwise. We will use this data to fulfill our agreement with you.
  2. We may use information that you provide or that is obtained by us:   

    * to register you with our website and to administer our website services;
    * or assessment and analysis (e.g. market, customer and product analysis) to enable us to review, develop and improve the services which we offer and to enable us to provide you and other customers with relevant information through our marketing programmed. We may use your information to make decisions about you using computerized technology, for example automatically selecting products or services which we think will interest you from the information we have. We may keep you informed of such products and services (including special offers, discounts, offers, competitions and so on) by any of the following methods:  

      * email
      * telephone (including automated calls)
      * SMS text message and other electronic messages such as picture messaging
      * post
      * fax
      * or otherwise
(including products and services of other companies and organizations) which we consider may be of interest to you. If you do not wish to receive information of such products and services, please tick the opt-out box provided when registering on this website.
  3. We may supplement the information that you provide to us with information that we receive from third parties.
  4. **Fraud Prevention**  
In order to protect our customers and us from fraud and theft, we may pass on information that we obtain from making identity checks and other information in our customer records, including how you conduct your account, to  other retailers and to financial and other organisations (including law enforcement agencies) involved in fraud prevention and detection, to use in the same way.
  5. **Disclosure of Your Information**  
We may give information about you to the following, who may use it for the same purposes as set out above:  

    * to employees and agents in  the  organization to administer any accounts, products and services provided to you by the Symbios.pk now or  in the future;
    * agents who (on our behalf) profile your data so that we may tailor the goods/services we offer to your specific needs;
    * to anyone to whom we transfer or may transfer our rights and duties under our agreement with you;
    * if we have a duty to do so or if the law allows us to do.
  6. **Security**  
We endeavour to take all reasonable steps to protect your personal information. However, we cannot guarantee the security of any data you disclose online. You accept the inherent security risks of providing information and dealing online over the Internet and will not hold us responsible for any breach of security unless this is due to our negligence or wilful default. 
  7. For further information about the steps we take to protect your information and make online shopping as secure as possible, please see information on [Secure online shopping](http://symbios.pk/%22http://www.argos.co.uk/static/StaticDisplay/includeName/Security.htm/%22 "\\"Secure").

  8. **General**  
Please be aware that our site may link to other websites which may be accessed through our site. We are not responsible for the data policies or procedures or the content of these linked websites.

**How can I get my name removed from the symbios.pk  mailing list?**

If you want to be removed from our mailing list, please send an email to [info@symbios.com.pk](http://symbios.pk/%22mailto:info@symbios.pk/%22) with the word \'remove\' in the subject line and the email address that you wish to be removed within the email. Please note that it may take up to 28 days to action your request.

This Policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically. We reserve the right to use or disclose your personally identifiable information for business reasons in whatever manner desired

**Contact Us**

If you have any comments or queries in connection with our privacy policy, please call 021-4140918 or simply write to us at[ info@symbios.pk](http://symbios.pk/%22mailto:info@symbios.pk/%22)
